debate.org 2019-03-30

# Privacy Statement | Debate.org

We at Debate.org, doing business as Juggle, LLC ("we" or "Juggle") have created this privacy policy to inform you of our commitment to protecting your personal information and inform you about how your personal information is handled. This privacy policy only applies to activity, transactions and data gathered from your activities on the Debate.org Website, between Debate.org members (collectively, the "Site") but does not apply to any other website or offline point of contact between Debate.org, Juggle, or any other company, and consumers.

## About Debate.org and the Information We Collect.

Debate.org is a membership-based online debating service designed to provide an easy and free system for our members to debate each other on the Web. To accomplish this, our members create their own unique profiles and our technology provides a "ratio of disagreement" with other members based on the information that is provided. In order to do this, we must ask for certain personal information, which may or may not include: customer-specified Debate.org username, gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, religion, occupation, preference/lifestyle information, geographic location, political affiliation and other various information. This information is used by visitors and members for searching and selecting a debate opponent. Much of this information is optional, and meant to be seen by other members and visitors. Public information supplied by the user is intended to be viewed by visitors to the site.

## Operational Communications

We may use your email address and other personal information to help us efficiently operate the Site, to contact you in connection with your activity on the Site (including, but not limited to, confirmation emails or important news that could affect your relationship with Debate.org), and to forward messages and debate challenges to you from other Debate.org users. These communications are known as "Operational Communications." These Operational Communications may also contain commercial messages, banner ads, newsletters, information, special offers and other promotional materials for Debate.org or third parties' goods or services. The Site provides you with options to decline to receive communications from Debate.org (other than those contained in Operational Communications). Some of these options may only be for a certain category of communications; others may be more general. By posting a profile on the Site, you are opting in to receive communications and offers sent by Debate.org.

## No Spam

We at Debate.org do not and will not send spam emails to email addresses entered into our website from one of our services. We will only use customer email addresses to contact and fulfill the services requested. We hold to a very strict no spam policy, since we are very much against spam ourselves. We do not sell, rent, share, trade, or give away any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission, in cases where you are expressly informed otherwise.

## Private Information

To accept new members, we may require information that includes, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, birth date, a user-specified username and password, country, state, and city. We primarily use email addresses submitted by members to verify enrollment. Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. We collect date of birth to help us ensure we provide the right experience for a user's age. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of Debate.org. Most private information can be updated by the user at any time. Except where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership.

## Minors & Safety

We take safety and privacy issues very seriously, particularly when they involve minors. Debate.org does not solicit membership for persons under the age of 13 nor are our services targeted towards minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a minor under the age of 13 has created an account and provided personal information, we will take the necessary steps to remove the information and delete the account. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [moderation@debate.org](mailto:moderation@debate.org).

## Legal

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud, situations involving potential physical threats to any person, violations of our "Terms of Use", or as otherwise required by law.

## Acquire or Transfer

We reserve the right to transfer information about you to a successor-in-interest that acquires the right to such information by acquiring the Service, acquiring Debate.org technology and member base or any or all of Juggle's assets pertaining to the Debate.org website, or merging with Juggle. In any of these events, Juggle will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Public Forums

Debate.org makes comments/message boards available to its users and all debates are public for members and visitors to view. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifying information.

## Links

This site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that Juggle is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Debate.org.

## Communications to Non-Members

When you choose to use the Debate.org "Invite friends" feature, you are prompted to input friend's email addresses. We will automatically send an email to the addresses provided, with a message inviting the recipient to join the Debate.org community. Abuse of this feature will result in automatic termination of your account.

## Security

All Member accounts are password-protected. We go to great lengths to protect the account information that you have provided us. Access to this information is limited to only the Juggle employees who need it in order to perform their job function, such as customer service representatives. However, please note that we do not guarantee account security. Hardware or software failure, unauthorized use, and other factors may lead to a security breach. If you have any questions about this, please contact us.

## Your IP Address

Each time you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the webpage from which you came. This is common practice for e-commerce websites in order to administer, optimize and to diagnose problems with our Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you, collect broad demographic information and to verify and track your session. This gives Juggle an idea of which parts of our site anonymous users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable.

## Third-Party Advertising

Advertisements seen on Debate.org are delivered to you by third-party advertising partners. These third parties may use cookies when showing you advertisements. These cookies may be used to determine on which website the third-party's advertisement was displayed, and whether or not the advertisement was clicked. This information helps our advertising partners deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be most relevant to you. We do not have access to the cookies placed by third parties. Our Privacy Policy applies only to Debate.org, and does not apply to the use of cookies by any third-party. We suggest that you review these third parties' privacy policies to learn about their cookies and other privacy practices.

## Use of Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects a cookie, they will not be able to use our site. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user.

## Email Choice/Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive email notifications from Debate.org, you may modify your account settings. In addition, every email that we send includes instructions directing the recipient how to opt-out of future emails sent from Debate.org.

## Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

Debate.org provides users the following options for modifying information previously submitted.

  1. Modify their account they created online from their account page.
  2. Send email via the "Contact Form" on the site.
  3. You can send mail to our postal address.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect or do not affect the user information already stored in our database, we will post the change on this page. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

## Contacting Juggle

If you have any questions about this User Agreement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the Debate.org website, you can contact:

Juggle, LLC  
#33 Bronze Pointe  
Suite 150  
Swansea, IL 62226, USA
